medical-look.com 2010-06-09

# Medical Look - Privacy Statement

The privacy policy herein refers to Medical-Look owned and operated websites and websites that Medical-Look retains control over. Websites that are hotlinked, advertiser websites, and websites that are not owned, operated, or controlled by Medical-Look retain their own privacy policy and Medical-Look does not condemn, condone, or influence third party website privacy policy. It is the user's responsibility to read the privacy policy of any third party website that is linked to or in any way associated with Medical-Look.

**Personally Identifiable Information**  
Medical Look does not collect Personally Identifiable Information without user knowledge. Personally Identifiable Information includes name, contact information, personal health information, or any information which can be used to personally identify the user. Users must take a reasonable action of knowledge, such as fill out information about themselves, in order to allow Medical-Look any Personal Identifiable Information. Medical-Look does not sell, trade, or in any other manner offer Personal Identifiable Information to any other website or other information collection agency, unless compelled by a court order. In the even that Medical-Look is forced by court order to hand over Personally Identifiable Information, every effort will be made to contact the user, unless prohibited by a matter of law. 

**Personally Identifiable Information**  
Medical look does collect Non-Personal Information through the use of cookies and web beacons. Non-Personal Information is information that can assist in identifying which features of the website are utilized, for how long, and for what purpose but does not give us any personal information which can be used to identify any particular user. Rejecting or accepting cookies is a function that the user can control through the settings option on their web browser or gives directions via the "Help" section of the browser. Users are not required to accept cookies in order to utilize the Medical-Look website, although there may be features that will not function properly if the user disables the cookies settings. Medical-Look does not condone, condemn, or influence the use of cookies or web beacons used by websites or advertiser sites that are linked to the Medical-Look website. It is the user's responsibility to understand the collection process of both Personally Identifiable Information as well as Non-Personal Information used by website or advertisers that are linked to the Medical-Look website.

**Un-secure Forums**  
Privacy policies do not apply to message boards, forums, or third party communications initiated by the user. These forums are for the purpose of open communication and do not assume privacy based on the open communication. All communication initiated by the user is determined by the user. Information the user wishes to express is the extent that privacy can be expected.

Website registration, email registration, and interactive tools require voluntarily providing Personally Identifiable Information. Personally Identifiable Information that is offered for any of these voluntary services requires an obvious action by the user and is limited to the information that the user themselves supplies.

**Minor Use**  
The Medical-Look website is not intended or designed to attract, interact with, or provide services to children under the age of 18. Medicalook will not knowingly interact with children under the age of 18. Medical-Look assumes no liability, however, for interactions with minors who deceive the Medical-Look website personnel into believing he or she is 18 or over. It is parental responsibility to know where children are interacting and with whom on the web.

**Removal of Personally Identifiable Information**  
The removal of Personally Identifiable Information requires the user to contact the appropriate department of Medical-Look for removal of voluntarily offered Personally Identifiable Information. Response to email requests may take 48 working hours. All e-mail requests are handled within a reasonable time frame.

**Internal Security**  
Internal security is very high. All employees and internal personnel are screened thoroughly and are required to handle personal information with the sensitivity it deserves. Internal personnel is subject to criminal prosecution in the event of breached security.
